A Finding Aid to the John Steuart Curry and Curry Family Papers, 1848-1999, bulk 1916-1946, in the Archives of American Art AAA.currjohn
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence and Project Files, 1928-1946; Series 3; (Boxes 1-3, OV 11; 2.3 linear feet)
  - Lea, Tom, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Life Magazine, 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    (Margit Varga)
  - Miscellaneous M, 1938-1946; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 58-59)
    (Russell Plumpton of Minneapolis Institute of the Arts, Glen Mitchell, Frederick Robinson of Museum of Fine Arts Springfield)
  - M.H. de Young Memorial Museum, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    (Walter Heil; see also Estate Papers)
  - Marsh, Reginald, 1938, 1940-1942, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    (first postcard in folder is a photocopy, location of the original is not known; file also contains technical notes and illustrated letters; see also Estate Papers)
  - Mathiesen, John, 1941-1946 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    (see also University of Wisconsin Rural Art Program)
  - McCloy, William, 1941-1946 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Meier, Norman C., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Men's Sketch Club of LaCrosse, Wisconsin, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1941, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    (Francis Henry Taylor)
  - Milwaukee Art Institute, 1943-1946 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous N-O, circa 1931945 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    (National Institute of Arts and Letters, Edward Alden Jewell and Howard De Vree of the New York Times, Newsweek)
  - National Academy of Design, 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Neville Public Museum (Green Bay, Wisconsin), 1943 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Nock, Sam, 1940-1946 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous P-Q, 1938-1945 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    (Lorene Payne with print reproductions enclosed, Lydia Bond Powel)
  - Pick, Stephen, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Permanent Pigments, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Miscellaneous R, 1938-1946 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    (Helen Appleton Read, Carroll Russell)
  - Rawlings, Marjorie Kinnan, 1940-1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ringling Brothers, 1933-1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    (Beverly Kelley)
  - River Falls State Teachers College, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    (Alberta Greene)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1938-1945; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    (Paul Sample, Mrs. Millard Smith)
  - Schmeckebier, Laurence, 1939-1944; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    (see also Estate Papers)
  - Simon and Schuster, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - State Teachers College (Eau Claire, WI), 1941 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous T, 1931, 1939-1946; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    (Ann Elgin and Arthur Northwood of Time, Inc., C.B. Porter of the Washington Times Herald, Margaret Treadwell)
  - Treasury Department, Section of Painting and Sculpture, circa 1934-1943 (Box 3, Folder 13-15)
    (Ed Rowan, Edward Bruce, Forbes Watson, Maria K. Ealand; also contains pamphlet "New Forces in American Art" by Watson)
  - Treasury Department, Section of Painting and Sculpture, Blueprints, 1935, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Treasury Department, Section of Painting and Sculpture, Contracts and Vouchers, 1935-1939 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous U-V, 1937-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    (Robert Von Neumann)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - University of Minnesota Farm and Home Week, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1936-1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    (Chris Christensen; contains a photograph, postcards, employment documents, documents related to law library mural, and article announcing Curry's appointment)
  - University of Wisconsin, Rural Art Program, circa 1934-1945; (4 folders; see also OV 11) (Box 3, Folder 22-25)
    (contains articles, clippings, catalogs, lists, and items related to exhibitions of rural artists in Wisconsin; clippings related to the appointment of Curry as artist-in-residence; poetry by Earl Sudgen; review of Curry's biography)
  - Upital, Frank, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    (Mrs. H.L. Burnham, Federated Women's Groups)
  - Miscellaneous W, 1937-1946 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
    (Wisconsin State Fair, Frank Lloyd Wright)
  - Walker Galleries, 1930-1941; (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 29-34)
    (contains inventories and price lists, an essay by Maynard Walker, documents related to transfer of inventory from Ferargil Galleries, consignment records, financial statements, Maynard Walker letters and third-party correspondence)
  - Washburn, Helen (Mrs. Kenneth), 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    (contains excerpt of article on Curry by Washburn)
  - Webster, Bethuel, circa 1938-1942 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    (legal correspondence)
  - Western Playing Card Company, 1941-1946 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - White, W.A., 1930-1942 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    (contains letters between Maynard Walker, W.A. White, and Mrs. H.J. Allen; see also Kansas State House Murals)
  - Whitney Museum, circa 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    (Juliana Force)
  - Whyte, Malcolm K., 1939-1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Wickey, Harry, 1931-1942 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Wisconsin Loan Exhibition, 1937-1938; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
    (contains catalog typescript, receipts, insurance records, clipping)
  - Wood, Grant, 1936-1942 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    (contains essay about Wood by Curry)
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1937, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Y-Z, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    (Stanley Young, Anita Zentner)
  - First Names Only and Unsigned, 1936-1945 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Oversized Materials from Correspondence and Project Files (see Box 3, folder 24) (Box 11 (OV))
- Subject Files, 1848-1946; Series 4; (Boxes 3-4, OV 11-12; 0.7 linear feet)
  This series contains clippings, photographs, prints, letters responding to research queries, a bibliography, notes, sketches, and other ephemera gathered by Curry. Many of the files consist entirely of images clipped from illustrated magazines and newspapers. Sketches are found in the Kansas history, Russell/Remington, and circus files. A series of snapshots in the circus files appear to have been taken by Curry. Other types of material found are noted in the folder listing.
  Subjects that are particularly well-developed in this series include American Indians, the circus, John Brown, and Kansas history. Many of the subjects are recognizable as subjects of Curry's artwork.
  Arrangement is alphabetical by subject. Headings added to subject files during reprocessing are indicated in brackets. Dates in the folder listing refer to dates of file contents; files appear to have been created between 1920 and 1946. Additional research and pictorial references gathered by Curry can be found in Correspondence and Project Files, Print Materials, and Photographs.
  - American Indians, circa 1848-1943; (5 folders; partially scanned; see also OV 11) (Box 3, Folder 48-52)
  - Circus (Box 3)
    - Photographs and Postcard, circa 1932, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 53)
      (Contains a photograph of Curry)
    - Negatives, circa 1932; (partially scanned) (Box 3, Folder 54)
      (Contains one unprinted image; other images exist in prints in previous folder)
    - Sketch, circa 1939 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Programs, circa 1930-1939; (partially scanned) (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Clippings, circa 1920-1946; (see also OV 12) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - John Brown, circa 1928-1940 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    (contains copy photographs, correspondence, and pamphlets)
  - [Chardin], undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    (contains print)
  - [Daumier], circa 1854-1857; (See OV 11) (Box 3, Folder 60)
    (contains satirical drawings printed in the illustrated French newspaper, le Charivari)
  - Delacroix, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Eskimos, circa 1920-1929, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Flags, 1932, 1941; (see OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Flowers, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - [Fourain, Jean-Louis], 1933, undated; (partially scanned) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    (contains a catalog and annotated photographs of sketches)
  - Harvesting, 1920-1938; (See also OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Interiors, circa 1927-1933 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kansas History, circa 1924-1938 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    (Contains sketches; correspondence with Henry Carey; snapshots including photographs of a tornado, floods, and animals; postcards; pamphlets; and clippings including a 1930 Saturday Evening Post series on Kansas.)
  - [Lynchings], 1933; (see OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Modern Painters, circa 1933-1943; (partially scanned; see also OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    (contains print materials related to Grant Wood, reproductions of works of art by various artists, and postcards, including one sent from Maynard Walker in 1936, and another unsigned postcard sent in 1933)
  - [Old Masters], undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Religious, 1934, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    (contains a pamphlet from a Canadian Christian wax museum)
  - Rubens, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Russell/Remington, circa 1907-1923; (See also OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    (Contains pen and pencil sketches, postcards)
  - Ships, circa 1929-1937 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    (contains a photograph)
  - Soldiers, circa 1918-1942; (See also OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - [Sports], circa 1918-1932; (See also OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - [Miscellaneous Subjects], circa 1928-1937; (See also OV 11) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Oversized Items from Subject Files (Box 3, folders 48 and 60; Box 4, folders 3, 6, 8, 9, 10, 14, 16, 17, 18) (Box OV 11)
  - Oversized Items from Subject Files (Box 3, folder 57) (Box OV 12)
- Notes and Writings, circa 1911-1946; Series 5; (Box 4; 0.3 linear feet)
  This series contains essays, notes, transcripts of lectures and interviews, and other miscellaneous writings written primarily by John Steuart Curry. Other authors, where known, are noted in the folder listing, along with details about subject content. Subjects of writings include art technique, art history, Curry's artworks, early school essays, and one brief essay on Grant Wood. Also found are an annotated address book and mailing list dating from Curry's years in Westport, Connecticut, and travel notes from his trip to Europe in 1926-1927.
  When multiple drafts are present, drafts are filed in the order in which they appear to have been written. Additional notes and writings are scattered throughout the collection.
  - Art Materials and Techniques (Box 4)
    - Maroger Medium, circa 1941 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "Sizing and Mounting of Linen Canvas for Mauroflased Wallpainting", circa 1940 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      (by Olle Nordmark)
    - "Some Methods and Materials to Prepare for Oil Painting", circa 1930-1939 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      (multiple drafts by Curry)
    - Miscellaneous Materials and Techniques, circa 1931-1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      (Includes correspondence with Martin Fischer; Beck, Koller and Co.; Benajmin Moore and Co.; Masonite Corporation; See also Correspondence and Project Files for Reginald Marsh and Helen "Pete" Farr)
  - Description of Murals for Kansas State House, circa 1937-1942 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    (multiple drafts)
  - Descriptions of Other Artworks by Curry, circa 1930-1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Essays (Box 4)
    - Essays by Curry, circa 1924-1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      (includes an autobiographical essay; essays on the creative process, art technique, and Grant Wood; see also Correspondence and Project Files)
    - Essays by Others about Curry, circa 1936-1946 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      (includes an essay by Chris L. Christensen; see also Estate Papers)
    - School Essays, circa 1911 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      (includes one illustrated essay by Curry)
  - Lectures on American Painting, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Notes from Slide Lecture on Art History, circa 1936-1946; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 29-30)
  - Radio Interview Transcript, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Works Progress Administration Recreation Project Questionnaire, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Annotated Address Book, circa 1924-1936 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Mailing Lists, circa 1924-1936, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Travel Notes from Europe, 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, circa 1923-1946 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Poems, 1937, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Personal Business Records, 1916-1952; Series 6; (Box 4, OV 13; 0.3 linear feet)
  This series contains documents related to John Steuart Curry's business transactions and personal finances. Records include contracts, account books, receipts, notes, correspondence, bills, bank statements, tax forms, stock certificates, deeds, copyright certificates, photographs, and lists of artwork. Curry's expenses in Chicago as a student are in a small, handwritten notebook. Later trips to Europe, Cuba, Panama, Kansas, and elsewhere are documented in notes, bills, statements, and receipts. Records of artwork include a small card file, photographs of artwork, copyright certificates, and lists of artwork, most of which appear to be related to exhibitions. Lists and inventories made after Curry's death are found in Estate Papers.
  Additional business records from Curry's lifetime are found in Correspondence and Project Files, and Estate Papers contain business records from after Curry's death. See also Notes and Writings for additional documentation of Curry's travels.
  - Contracts and Agreements, 1936, 1941, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Engagement Calendar, 1937-1938, 1942-1944 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    (annotated)
  - Expense Accounts (Box 4)
    - Chicago, circa 1916 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Cuba and Panama, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Europe, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous Accounts and Receipts, circa 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Insurance, 1935-1952 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Personal Financial Records (Box 4)
    - Bank Records, 1940-1946; (not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Consumers' Cooperative of Wisconsin, circa 1941-1951; (not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Legal Documents, 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Taxes, 1938-1951; (not scanned) (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
  - Records of Artwork (Box 4)
    - Card File, circa 1923-1945 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Copyright Certificates and Card File, 1937-1946 (Box 4, Folder 51-53)
    - Lists of Artwork, circa 1930-1939, 1946; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 54)
      (See also Inventories in Estate Papers for lists compiled after 1946)
  - Oversized List of Artwork (from Box 4, f54) (Box OV 13)
- Print Materials, 1918-1985; Series 7; (Boxes 4-5, 10; OV 12-13; 1.6 linear feet)
  This series contains exhibition catalogs, clippings, periodicals, book illustrations, magazine illustrations, printed reproductions of artwork, monographs about Curry, scrapbooks created by Curry and his relatives, and other miscellany. This series includes print materials gathered during Curry's lifetime and after his death.
  Magazine illustrations include some of Curry's early commercial artwork from illustrated magazines such as Country Gentleman, Boy's Life, and Western Weekly. The first magazine illustration in the series is annotated indicating that it was Curry's first illustration. Clippings are mostly related to Curry's artwork, his residency at the University of Wisconsin, and his death in 1946.
  Exhibition catalogs are from Curry's solo and group exhibitions. Early catalogs contain some annotations. Reproductions of Curry's paintings and drawings are found in a variety of media including book and magazine covers, pamphlets, and advertisements.
  John Steuart Curry's childhood scrapbook contains clippings from pictorial magazines, photographs of livestock, and a couple of sketches. Later scrapbooks kept by his wife, sister, and brother are also found, and contain mostly clippings.
  Articles about Curry found in the periodicals are duplicated in clippings. Additional print materials are found throughout the collection. See series descriptions for further details.
  - Book Illustrations, circa 1940-1946 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Magazine Illustrations, circa 1921-1926; (3 folders; see also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 56-58)
  - Clippings, circa 1918-1919, 1929-1931; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Clippings, 1933-1936; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Clippings, 1937-1938; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Clippings, 1939; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Clippings, 1940; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Clippings, 1941; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Clippings, 1942; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Clippings, 1943; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Clippings, 1944-1945; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Clippings, 1946; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Clippings, 1947-1949; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Clippings, 1950-1952; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Clippings, 1953-59; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Clippings, 1960-1969; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Clippings, 1970-1975; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Clippings, 1976-1978; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Clippings, 1981-1988; (See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Clippings, undated; (2 folders; See also OV 13) (Box 4, Folder 76-77)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1930-1939; (partially scanned) (Box 4, Folder 78)
    (Contains some annotations)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, 1940-1992, undated; (9 folders; partially scanned) (Box 5, Folder 1-9)
  - Monographs about Curry (Box 5)
    - Scribner's Examines: John Steuart Curry by Thomas Craven, 1938; (partially scanned) (Box 5, Folder 10)
      (production copy; also contains production copy of related pamphlet)
    - List of Illustrations for John Steuart Curry: Pageant of America, circa 1943; (not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - American Artists Group Monograph, 1945; (not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pamphlets Related to Art Materials and Techniques, 1928, undated; (partially scanned) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets Related to Kansas, circa 1950-1980; (not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Periodicals, (not scanned; see Clippings) (Box 5)
    - America 200, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - American Artist, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Art In America, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Demcourier, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Kansas Directory, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Kansas Magazine, 1941, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Kansas Quarterly, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Life, 1936, 1946; (See Box 10, sol) (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Register of the Museum of Art (University of Kansas), 1959 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Scribner's Magazine, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Time, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Wisconsin Alumnus, 1949, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Reproductions of Artwork (Box 5)
    - Covers, circa 1938-1975; (partially scanned; see also OV 12) (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Lucky Strike Advertisements, circa 1942 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - War Bonds Advertisements, circa 1941-1945; (See also OV 12) (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Pamphlets, circa 1935-1964 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Proofs and Prints, undated; (not scanned; see also OV 12) (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Reproductions, crica 1930-1985; (not scanned; see also OV 12) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Scrapbooks (Box 5)
    - John Steuart Curry, circa 1905-1907 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      (Contains clippings, childhood sketches, and photographs of livestock)
    - Margery Curry Fike (sister), 1937-1936; (See Box 10, sol) (Box 5, Folder 34)
      (Contains clippings)
    - Kathleen Curry (wife), 1935-1940; (See Box 10, sol) (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - R. Eugene Curry (brother), 1936-1939, 1946; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
  - Miscellaneous Print Materials, circa 1939-1986; (partially scanned) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Oversized Periodicals (from Box 5, folder 22) (Box 10)
  - Oversized Scrapbooks (from Box 5, folders 34-36) (Box 10)
  - Oversized Reproductions of Artwork (from Box 5, folders 27, 28, 31, 32) (Box OV 12)
  - Oversized Magazine Illustrations (from Box 4, folder 58) (Box OV 13)
  - Oversized Clippings (from Box 4, folders 59-77) (Box OV 13)
- Photographs, circa 1900-1998; Series 8; (Boxes 5-6, OV 14; 1.1 linear feet)
  This series includes photographs of John Steuart Curry and his family, friends, colleagues, homes, and artwork. Photographs of Curry include formal portraits, publicity photographs, candid photographs, and snapshots. Notable subjects include a significant number of photographs showing Curry working on and posing with artwork, and many early photographs of Curry as a young athlete. Additional information about the subject matter of photographs is included in the folder listing.
  Many of the photographs of works of art appear to have been made and maintained by Kathleen Curry, who owned the reproduction rights of her husband's artwork, and handled copyright permissions for the estate for many decades. Some of the earlier photographs of paintings are annotated with names of owners and information about their subjects which appears to be in Curry's handwriting.
  Additional records related to Kathleen Curry's work with her husband's estate are found in Estate Papers. Additional information about copyright is also found in Personal Business Records.
  Additional photographs are found throughout the collection. In particular, photographs of the circus, which appear to have been taken by Curry and include a photograph of Curry, are found in the Subject Files.
  - Formal Portraits of John Steuart Curry, circa 1918-1943; (2 folders; copies not scanned; see also OV 14) (Box 5, Folder 39-40)
  - Candid Photographs of JSC, circa 1930-1946 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - JSC in the Studio, Drawing, and Painting, circa 1918-1944; (see also OV 14) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - JSC Posing with Artwork, circa 1930-1946; (3 folders; copies not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - JSC with Grant Wood and Thomas Hart Benton, circa 1932-1938; (2 folders; copies not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - JSC with Other Artists, circa 1918-1945 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - JSC Sitting on Juries, circa 1932-1938 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - JSC during Army Medical Department Art Project, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - JSC's Wisconsin Radio Appearance, circa 1936-1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Family Photographs, circa 1900-1950 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    (Includes group photograph of Curry as baby with sisters; For images of Curry painting with his step-daughter present, see JSC in Studio, Drawing, and Painting)
  - Class Photograph, circa 1913-1919 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Curry Homes in Madison and Westport, circa 1939, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - JSC and Kathleen Curry, circa 1939, 1941; (2 folders; copies not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 13-14)
  - Athletics (Box 6)
    - Team Portraits, circa 1913-1919 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Action Shots, circa 1915-1919, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hunting, Riding, Camping, Fishing, circa 1918-1942; (See also OV 14) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Snapshots, circa 1913-1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Groups, circa 1930-1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Places, circa 1929-1930 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Photographs of Works of Art (Box 6)
    - Drawings, Paintings, and Prints, (not scanned) (Box 6)
      - Animals, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Army Medical Art Project, circa 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Figures, undated; (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 23-26)
      - Illustrations, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Landscapes, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Portraits, undated; (See also OV 14) (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Still Life, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition Views, circa 1943-1990, undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Hand-Painted Wedding Chest (circa 1934), undated; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Murals (Box 6)
      - Connecticut Murals (1934), undated; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Department of the Interior Building (1938), undated; (not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 34)